翻译 & 压制 by Mr. Kin
Blender工作室 出品
你好  蜗牛先生
Hello, Mr. Snail!
散大蜗牛：俗名花园蜗牛（garden snail)
学名：cornu aspersum
哦  你这个小可爱  散大蜗牛
Aw, you cute little cornu aspersum.
拉丁名字  加分
Latin name, a bonus point!
抱树者：意指给环保主义者贴上过于情绪化和不理性的标签
不敢相信我们和抱树者被困在一起了
Can't believe we got stuck with the tree hugger.
如果我不得不再听到一种动物的拉丁名字，我发誓我会宰了她
If I have to hear the latin name for one more animal, I swear I'm gonna kill her.
放松点  亲爱的  在她做所有工作时，我们就能享受所有乐趣了
Relax, sugar buns. While she does all the work, we'll have all the fun.
对  然后喝得酩酊大醉
Yeah! And get wasted out of our minds!
遥遥领先于你  伙计
Way ahead of you, man.
快点儿  大伙们  有这么多的自然风光可看，我们可不能磨磨蹭蹭
Come on, team! We mustn't dilly-dally when there's so much nature to see!
我在考虑，我们应该把我们的班级项目称为“森林里的真菌”
I was thinking we should call our class project, “Fungis in a Forest”
fungis和fun guys同音
fungi本身是复数，此处加s应该是为了配合台词
明白吗？因为我们是一群有趣的人
Get it? Because we're a group of fun guys.
而且真菌……
And also fungis which...
嘘  那是一只黄鹡鸰  而且她遭遇危难了
Shush! That's a yellow wagtail. And she's in distress!
黄鹡鸰学名：motacilla flava
该学名指的是西方黄鹡鸰（western yellow wagtail）
好了  好了  我的小黄鹡鸰
There, there, my little motacilla flava.
哦  看看她飞的样子
Oh! Look at her go!
哇
Wow!
别挡道  呆子  我们要在这里露营
Out of the way, dorkwad! We're camping here.
总算到了  是时候开始烧烤野餐了
Finally! Time to get that BBQ burning.
噢  天哪
Oh. Oh, dear.
恶心
Gross!
噢  悠着点  大伙们  我们应当研究自然，而不是破坏它
Oh. Easy, guys. We're supposed to be studying nature, not wrecking it.
小便，休息
Piss break!
嘿  真菌怪胎  别闲着，来安装帐篷
Oy, fungus freak! Make yourself useful and fix the tent.
哦  有点友好的营地笑话  有趣
Oh, a bit of friendly campsite ribbing. Fun.
她一个人在这片树林里活不过五分钟
She wouldn't survive 5 minutes alone in these woods.
对  她是一个真正的窝囊废，不是吗？
Yeah. She's a real weenie that one, innit?
嘿  菲尔  那些香肠怎么样了？
Oy, Phil! How those sausages coming?
差不多好了  只需再加点盐
Almost ready! Just need a bit more salt.
太不可思议了  这是一个新物种
It's incredible. It's a new species.
那些到底是什么鬼东西？
What the bloody hell are those things?
gnome：童话故事中的地下宝藏守护神，外形像戴着尖顶帽的小人
这就像一个守护精灵头顶一只蘑菇
It's like a gnome shagged a mushroom.
他们极其可爱
They're absolutely adorable.
是的  绝对很可爱
Yeah, absolutely bloody adorable.
我敢打赌，如果我们抓住其中的一个，就能发大财了
And I bet we'll make a fortune if we catch one of those things.
我们会出名的
We'd be famous!
上电视
Get on MTV.
我想知道它们是什么味道
I wonder what they taste like.
我们真的不应该破坏它们的栖息地
We really shouldn't disrupt their habitat.
对  当然 当然
Right. Sure, sure.
你们好
Greetings.
欢迎，朋友们
Welcome, friends.
我马上就下来
I'll be right down.
请你们喝一些薄荷茶，可以吗？
Could I interest you in some peppermint tea?
你们是什么东西？
What are you guys?
我们是小精灵  我们让森林保持平衡
We are Sprites. We sprite balance to the forest.
我们照看动物、植物、鸟类、苔藓……
We take care of the animals, plants, birds, moss...
大伙们？大伙们  我……
Guys? Guys, I...
嘿  呃  小蘑菇怪老头  我们在这里露营过夜，你能接受吗？
Hey, uh, little mushroom geezer, you cool with us camping here for the night?
当然  森林的朋友就是小精灵的朋友
Absolutely. A friend of the forest is a friend of the sprites.
也许只是番茄酱……  或者什么……  比如……
Maybe it was just ketchup... or something... like...
红色涂料？对  也许他们只是在给他们的小帽子涂颜料或者……  其他什么……
Red paint? Yeah, maybe they were just painting their little hats or... something...
大伙们？
Guys?
大伙们  这不好笑
Guys, this isn't funny.
大伙们？
Guys?
我们只是想抓住一个  但他们是神经病
We were just gonna catch one! But they're psycho!
快解开我  快点  他们会杀了我们的
You gotta get me outta these! Hurry! They're gonna kill us!
快点
Hurry!
♪ 右脚 左脚 树叶和石头 ♪
♪ Right foot, left foot, leaf and stone. ♪
你们选错露营地点了  贱人们
You picked the wrong camping spot, bitches.
净化他们
Sprite them!
跑
Run!!!
啊啊  我的眼睛
Aaaah! My eyes!
亲爱的  救我
Sugar Buns?! Help me!
宝贝儿
Sweet cakes!
亲爱的……
Love muffin...
嗯？
Huh?
什么？那是？
What? Is that?
不
No!!!
不不不  我不会游泳  我不会游泳
No, no, no! I can't swim! I can't swim!
太好了
Yes!
不
No!
同 son of a bitch
狗娘养的
Son of a Spriteberry!
好烫  好烫
It burns! It burns!
我不想伤害你们  只要离我远点就好了
I don't want to hurt you! Just keep your distance!
好吧  那就吃盐吧  你们这些绿色的小混蛋
All right, then. Eat salt, you little green bastards!
这可不行
Nah-uh-uh.
那些小流氓把世界当成他们自己的垃圾桶
Those punks treated the world as their own personal rubbish bin.
而你让他们获得自由
And you set them free!
现在你跟他们一起死吧
Now you'll join them!
迟早会还给你的 小鸟兄
I'll give you that one, Brother Bird!
好的  小精灵们  让我们烧掉尸体，然后喝点薄荷茶
Alright sprites, let's burn the bodies and have some peppermint tea.